{
  "version": 2.0,
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "In PAGE, acrylamide and ________ polymerize to form the gel in SDS-PAGE.",
      "answers": {
        "a": "answer1",
        "b": "answer2",
        "c": "answer3",
        "d": "answer4"
      },
     
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is a Sample Question 2?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "answer1",
        "b": "answer2",
        "c": "answer3",
        "d": "answer4"
      },
     
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is a Sample Question 2?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "answer1",
        "b": "answer2",
        "c": "answer3",
        "d": "answer4"
      },
     
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is a Sample Question 2?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "answer1",
        "b": "answer2",
        "c": "answer3",
        "d": "answer4"
      },
     
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is a Sample Question 2?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "answer1",
        "b": "answer2",
        "c": "answer3",
        "d": "answer4"
      },
     
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is a Sample Question 2?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "answer1",
        "b": "answer2",
        "c": "answer3",
        "d": "answer4"
      },
     
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is a Sample Question 2?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "answer1",
        "b": "answer2",
        "c": "answer3",
        "d": "answer4"
      },
     
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is a Sample Question 2?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "answer1",
        "b": "answer2",
        "c": "answer3",
        "d": "answer4"
      },
     
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is a Sample Question 2?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "answer1",
        "b": "answer2",
        "c": "answer3",
        "d": "answer4"
      },
     
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is a Sample Question 2?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "answer1",
        "b": "answer2",
        "c": "answer3",
        "d": "answer4"
      },
     
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": "beginner"
    }
  ]
}
